Guide to the Brooklyn For Peace records 2016.026
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn For Peace records
1983-2018
2002-2016
Brooklyn Historical Society
Brooklyn For Peace
Phillips, Charlotte
2016.026
25.5 Linear Feet in 40 manuscript boxes, 7 media boxes, 4 oversize rolls, 1 oversize flat box and 1 oversize flat file folder.
95 Cassettes
167 items (DVDs)
10 items (VHS)
7 items (CDs)
1 item (120 GB Hard Drive)
Brooklyn For Peace (BFP) was founded in 1984 as Brooklyn Parents for Peace by Charlotte Phillips and Carolyn Eisenberg, in response to the invasion of Grenada by the United States. Through public events, publicity campaigns, lobbying of elected officials, and demonstrations, Brooklyn For Peace works to eliminate war and the social injustices that are its causes. BFP's records reveal both the history of the organization as well as the broader grassroots response to a wide variety of significant social and political issues at the local, regional and national levels from the late twentieth century to the present.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Charlotte Phillips in 2016. A second accretion of material was delivered in 2018.
Appraisal
Duplicates of event flyers and routine correspondence were removed from the collection, as were newspaper and magazine clippings, receipts, blank forms, and other material not related to the interests and work of Brooklyn For Peace. Recordings of commerical broadcasts were removed from the collection.
Conditions Governing Access
The majority of this collection is open to research. A small portion of materials containing personally identifying information have been restricted, at the request of the donor, for a period of 30 years from the date of creation. Audiovisual material in this collection is not currently avaialble to researchers.
Scope and Contents
The Brooklyn For Peace records document the founding and ongoing activities of a Brooklyn-based community organization, Brooklyn For Peace (formerly Brooklyn Parents for Peace), covering the years 1984-2018. With over thirty years of work as a New York-based activist organization, BFP's institutional records reveal both the history of the organization as well as the grassroots response to a wide variety of significant social and political issues at the local, regional and national levels from the late twentieth century to the present. In particular, the records document BFP's organizational structure, key campaigns and projects, public events, and petitions circulated. These topics are represented through meeting minutes, mailings, internal correspondence, financial records, audio-visual material, and event ephemera including flyers, artwork and banners. The collection also includes substantial documentation of other local, regional and international organizations and individuals, through extensive subject files collected by BFP's leadership. Social and political issues that are particularly well represented in the collection include the campaign for nuclear disarmament, anti-war organizing from the Gulf War through the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq, and the Israel-Palestine conflict.
Biographical / Historical
Brooklyn For Peace (BFP) was founded in 1984 as Brooklyn Parents for Peace by Charlotte Phillips and Carolyn Eisenberg, in response to the invasion of Grenada by the United States. Since then, through public events, publicity campaigns, lobbying of elected officials, and demonstrations, Brooklyn For Peace has worked to eliminate war and the social injustices that are its causes. The organization works on domestic and international issues in an attempt to create a peaceful future. BFP operates as a membership-based, democratic, non-partisan, 501(c)3 corporation run by a Board of Directors.
Over the course of thirty years, BFP has worked on a wide range of issues pertaining to local, regional and international peace issues. BFP's committees have included: Arts and Culture, Anti-militarism (counter-recruitment), Climate Action, Darfur/Africa, Diversity and Outreach, Fundraising, International Law, Israel-Palestine, Latin America, Nuclear Zero, Peace and Economic Justice, Peace Fair, and UNICEF. There are several affiliated neighborhood-focused peace groups in the Brooklyn neighborhoods of Bay Ridge, Flatbush, Fort Greene, and Prospect-Lefferts Gardens. Regular efforts of BFP include organizing community meetings and forums, staffing information tables at relevant community and regional events, participating in phone and advertising campaigns, lobbying elected officials, participating in demonstrations, and providing didactic materials pertaining to targeted areas that fall within the mission of the organization.
BFP's earliest projects included organizing local opposition to a proposed Staten Island port for nuclear-capable cruise missiles, as well as protesting U.S. interventions in Central America and the 1991 Gulf War. Following September 11th, BFP advocated for the protection of civil liberties and opposed the detention of immigrants. In response to the No Child Left Behind Act in 2001, BFP sought to limit military recruiting in New York City public schools. This included distributing leaflets such as "How to Go to College Without Joining the Military."
BFP has organized against the wars in Iraq, Iran, Syria, Yemen, and Afghanistan, against police brutality in New York City, and for a peaceful solution to the Israel-Palestine conflict. More recently, BFP has joined in community opposition to fracking, to the Rockaway Pipeline, and to the Liquefied Natural Gas port on Long Island. From 2003 until 2012 BFP hosted a regular Peace and Justice Fair. The Peace Fair included musical and theater performances, educational sessions and discussions, and was primarily intended as an outreach forum. In 2013 the event was replaced by the Pathmakers to Peace Gala. Additionally, since 2006 BFP has hosted a monthly program "War No More" on BRIC's Brooklyn Community Access TV station.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into five series:
Series 1: Administration, 1985-2018
Series 2: Scrapbooks, 2003-2016
Series 3: Events, 1988-2017
Series 4: War No More Program, 2006-2012
Series 5: Subject Files, 1986-2017
Series 6: Petitions, 1985-2015
Related Materials
Arnie Goldwag Brooklyn Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) collection (ARC.002)
Bob Adelman photographs of Brooklyn Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) demonstrations (V1989.022)
Brooklyn neighborhood associations and civic organizations publications (ARC.167)
Eastern Parkway Coalition records (2007.016)
Sarita Daftary-Steel collection of East New York oral histories (2015.011)
B.A.N.G. Notes newsletters (BCMS.0091)
Afghan War, 2001-; Arab-Israeli conflict; Civic leaders |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Climatic changes; Community activists -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Counter-recruitment |z New York (State) |z New York; Festivals |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Iraq War, 2003-2011; Nuclear disarmament -- United States; Peace movements |z United States |x History; Persian Gulf War, 1991; Social movements |z New York (State) |z New York; Women and peace |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Correspondence; Ephemera; Political posters; Scrapbooks; Israeli-Palestinian conflict; Phillips, Charlotte; United for Peace and Justice; UNICEF; Brooklyn For Peace
- Series 1: Adminstration, 1985-2018; 5 Linear Feet in 12 manuscript boxes and 1 oversize folder.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains materials pertaining to the administration of Brooklyn fFor Peace from its founding in 1984 until the present. This includes correspondence and minutes of the Executive Board, committee correspondence and project files, and financial records and fundraising endeavors. Records from the Israel-Palestine Committee are particularly well represented. This series also includes general administrative records including correspondence regarding event endorsements, membership lists and special events, as well as office materials including organizational appointment books and notebooks. Finally, this series includes administrative records pertaining to the organization of the annual Peace Fair.
  Arrangement
  This series has been arranged into fice sub-series. Material has been grouped by subject and arranged alphabetically, with the exception of Sub-Series IA: Executive Board Meetings and Minutes, which is arranged chronologically.
  - Sub-Series IA: Executive Board Meetings and Minutes, 1985-2017
    - Coordinating Committee, circa 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Executive Board Minutes and Correspondence, 1991-2003 (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
    - Executive Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2004-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1-6)
    - Executive Board Minutes and Correspondence, 2009-2017 (Box 1, Folder 2-8)
  - Sub-Series IB: Committees, 2000-2017
    - Anti-Militarism Committee, 1991-2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Arts and Culture Committee, 2011-2016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Climate Change Committee, 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Darfur Crisis Committee, 2004-2017 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
    - Diversity Committee, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising Committee, 2003-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Iraq Committee, 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Boycott, Divestment, and Sanctions, 2009-2012 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Brooklyn College, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Gaza, 2006-2014 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Internal Communication, 2002-2011 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted until 2041.
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Lobbying, 2002-2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Meetings, 2003-2015 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Outreach, 2003-2013 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Israel and Palestine Committee - Statement, 2002-2014 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Latin American Committee, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear Zero Committee, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Nuclear Zero Committee Fact Sheets, 2007-2012 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Peace and Economic Justice Committee, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Political Representative Committtee, 2000-2017 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - UNICEF Committee, 2004-2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series IC: Financial and Fundraising Records, 1993-2014
    - 501(c)3 Status, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Financial Reports, 2004-2014 (Box 3, Folder 5-13)
    - Financial Reports, 1988-2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising, 2004-2014 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Grace Paley Summer Sunset on the Barge Fundraiser, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Grants, 1993-2014 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Grant Proposals - Brooklyn Arts Council, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - Grant Proposals - Rejections, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Grant Proposals - Public Freedom Fund, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Grants - State Education Department, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Grants - United States Institute for Peace, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Service Audit, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - International Center for Tolerance Education Fundraiser, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Jane Kurinsky Bequeath, 2017 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Pathmakers to Peace, 2013-2016 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Pass Through Grants, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Silent Auction Bid Sheets, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Summer Sunset on the Barge Fundraiser, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Summer Sunset on the Barge Fundraiser Host Committee, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Summer Sunset on the Barge Fundraiser Tickets, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Sunset Under the Barge Fundraiser Attendance, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - T-Shirt Sales, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series ID: Administrative Records, 1985-2017
    - Administrative Correspondence, 2000-2014 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Anti-War March on Washington, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Arts Workshop Sign-In Forms, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - BCAT War No More Program, 2006-2015 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Calendars, 2005-2016 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Capacity Building, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte Phillips Interviews, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Connections Newsletter, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Courier Life - No to War Against Iraq Ad, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Dance Concert for Peace, circa 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Restricted until 2020.
    - Distributed Articles, circa 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Event Attendence, 2009-2012 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Event and Endorsement Correspondence, 1998-2014 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Restricted until 2044.
    - Event and Endorsement Correspondence, 2003-2016 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Restricted until 2046.
    - Hard Drive, undated (Box 49)
      This item is not currently available to researchers.
    - Howard Zinn Event, circa 2004 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Insurance Policies, 2006-2007 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Materials for the Arts, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Membership Forms, 2000-2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Membership Lists, 1980-2018 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
      Restricted until 2048.
    - Membership Lists, 1980-2018 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Memorial Events, 2009-2013 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Administrative Records, 2003-2014 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - National March to Stop the War on Iraq, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1985-2014 (Box 46, Folder 11-12)
    - Notebooks, 1984-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3-7)
    - Notes, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Open Meetings, 1987-2012 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Open Meetings and Minutes, 1994-1999 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Organizational Guidelines, circa 2010 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Outreach Mailings, 1989-2017 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - Outreach Materials, 1995-2008 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Outreach Materials Original Copies, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Parenting Workshop, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Parrot Photographs (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Performance Agreements, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Restricted until 2039.
    - Phone Tree, 1990-2005 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      Restricted until 2035.
    - Photographs, 1980-2012 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Poems and Chants, 1980-2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Political Correspondence, 1997-2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Press Lists, 1991, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Press Releases, 1990-2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Program Coordinator Job Description, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Publications Related to BFP, 1986-2016 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Stop and Frisk: A Community Forum Release Forms, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Tabling, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Restricted until 2037.
    - Thank You Notes, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - United for Peace and Justice Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
      Restricted until 2038.
    - Volunteers, 2003-2006 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      Restricted until 2036.
    - Work o' the Weavers Concert, 2006 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series IE: Brooklyn Peace Fair, 2003-2015
    - Administration, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Advertisments, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Outreach Materials, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Peace Fair Day in Brooklyn Proclamation, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Administration, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - General Feedback Survey, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Outreach Materials, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Park Slope Jewish Center, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Participant Surveys, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Advertisements, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Administration, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Fundraising, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - General Feedback Surveys, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Outreach Contact Sheets, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
    - Outreach Materials, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Participating Organizations Survey, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Tables, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Administration, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
    - Outreach Materials, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Sponsorships, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Volunteers, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Youth Peace Contest, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn Peace Fair, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Administration, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - General Feedback Surveys, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Outreach Materials, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Administration, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Administration, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Outreach Materials, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Administration, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Administration, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Outreach Materials, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Administration, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - General Feedback Surveys, 2005-2015 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Committee and Participant Information, 2003-2008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Posters, 2005-2012 (Box 37, Folder 2, Flat file folder 1)
    - The End Peace Fair, undated (Box 39, Cassette 75)
- Series 2: Scrapbooks, 2003-2016; 3 Linear Feet in 7 manuscript boxes.
  Compiled by BFP leadership, this series includes 20 dated volumes of material representing the work of the organization, including events, meetings, discussions, interests, and conflicts. Material in this series consists primarily of event ephemera, newspaper clippings, informational pamphlets, correspondence, Brooklyn-based publications, and a small amount of administrative records. Volumes are organized by time period and cover BFP's involvement in the community throughout their existence, with a focus on the years 2003 through 2011. This series offers an overview of what BFP was doing in the community, what interested them as an organization, and what BFP's leadership felt was important to represent and document as an organization.
  Material in this series has been arranged chronologically.
  - Prior to 2003, 1971-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Volume 1, 1987-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Volume 2, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Volume 3, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Volume 4, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
  - Volume 5, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Volume 5, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Volume 7, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2-3)
  - Volume 8, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
  - Volume 9, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
  - Volume 10, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Volume 10, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Volume 11, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 3-6)
  - Volume 12, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Volume 12, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Volume 13, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2-5)
  - Volume 14, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
  - Volume 14, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Volume 15, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 3-6)
  - Volume 16, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Volume 16, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
  - Volume 17, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 4-7)
  - Volume 18, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
  - Volume 19, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 5-7)
- Series 3: Events, 1988-2017; 4.48 Linear Feet in 1 and a half manuscript boxes, 7 media boxes and 1 oversize folder.
  This series includes materials and recordings from events that BFP organized from their founding through 2018, addressing local, national, and international topics and conflicts. Ephemeral material in this series consists primarily of publicity mailings, event announcements and invitations, informational leaflets, program pamphlets, community outreach material, program and event descriptions and signs, as well as lobbying and propaganda material. Event recordings include cassettes, CD, VHS and DVD recordings of panel discussions, protests, and the Brooklyn Peace Fair. Subjects that are well represented are the Israel-Palestine conflict, the role of money in politics, local and national climate policy, and nuclear disarmament. Topics ranged from the local level, with interests such as the effort to shut down Indian Point, to international concerns in South Africa, Japan, Latin America, and the Middle East.
  Ephemera has been grouped by subject and arranged alphabetically. Audio-visual records are arranged alphabetically.
  - Sub-Series 3A: Brooklyn For Peace Event Ephemera, 1989-2017
    - Afghanistan, 2002-2011 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Anti-War Banners, circa 2000s (Object Roll 4)
    - Anti-War March on Washington, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Brooklyn For Peace Cloth Banners by Margaret Cusack, 1985 (Object Roll 1, Object Roll 2)
    - Brooklyn For Peace Vinyl Banners (3 items), undated (Object Roll 3)
    - Darfur and South Sudan, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Drones and Government Intelligence Agency, 2011-2013 (Box 17, Folder 10, Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Civil Liberties, 1990-2017 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Climate Policy, 2014-2017 (Box 17, Folder 12, Flat file folder 1)
    - Cultural Events, 1988-2011 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Europe, circa 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Fracking, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 15, Flat file folder 1)
    - Iraq, 1992-2014 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Iran, 2007-2012 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Israel and Palestine, 2001-2015 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Japan, 2015 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Latin America, 1986-2011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Middle East, 1990-2015 (Box 18, Folder 6, Flat file folder 1)
    - Military, 2002-2013 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Money and Politics, 1992-2017 (Box 18, Folder 8, Flat file folder 1)
    - New York City, 1995-2013 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - No Nuclear Weapons Event Photographs, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Policy, 1987-2017 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - New York Police Department, 2003-2014 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Pathmakers to Peace, 2013-2017 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Refugees and Immigrants, 2006-2017 (Box 18, Folder 13, Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Schools and Children, 1990-2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - South Africa, circa 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Syria, 2013-2017 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - UNICEF, circa 2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Vietnam, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - War, 1988-2017 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Yemen, circa 2017 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 3B: Event Recordings, 1991-2016
    - 5th Grade L.O.D, undated (Box 39, Cassette 68)
    - A Day in the Life of a Local Peace Activist DVD, 2005 (Box 43)
    - Afghanistan DVD, 2009 (Box 43)
    - Afghanistan Forum DVD, 2010 (Box 43)
    - African American Coalition on Mideast War, undated (Box 38, Cassette 3)
    - Alice Rothcild at the Brooklyn Society for Ethical Culture, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 79)
    - Alice VHS, undated (Box 40)
    - America's Military Today: The Challenge of Militarism at the CUNY Graduate Center DVD, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Amy Goodman at Pathmakers to Peace DVD, 2015 (Box 42)
    - A New Cold War - U.S., NATO, and Putin at the Brooklyn Commons DVD, 2016 (Box 42)
    - Annual Fundraiser Summer Sunset on the Barge DVD, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Anti-War Protest Photos CD, 2005 (Box 44)
    - Apathy by Harold Seletsky, undated (Box 38, Cassette 1)
    - Apartheid From South Africa to Palestine DVD, 2008 (Box 43)
    - Arab Spring DVD, 2011 (Box 41)
    - Arts and Activism, Darfur, Sudan Full Length DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Arts and Activism DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Art Activism, Brooklyn For Peace Forum, Full Length and Unedited DVD, 2013 (Box 41)
    - Barge Photos DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Boycott, Divestment and Sanctions on BCAT Copy DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - Boycott, Divestment and Sanctions Forum DVD, 2010 (Box 42)
    - Brooklyn Parents for Peace Protest CD, 2006 (Box 44)
    - Brooklyn Borough Hall Rally DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Brooklyn For Peace DVD, 2007 (Box 39, Cassette 88)
    - Brooklyn For Peace, Peace March DVD, 2007 (Box 44)
    - Brooklyn For Peace Presents Medea Benjamin the Pathmaker to Peace Award DVD, 2014 (Box 42)
    - Black Veterans for Social JusticeSalutes The National Association for Black Veterans, Gala on the Sea DVD, undated (Box 42)
    - BLS DVD, 2010 (Box 42)
    - Boycott and Divestment DVD, undated (Box 43)
    - Boycott and Divestment DVD, 2010 (Box 42)